<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Coffee Companion</string>
    <string name="title_activity_brew_method">BrewMethodActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_chemex">Chemex</string>
    <string name="title_activity_aeropress">Aeropress</string>
    <string name="title_activity_hario_v60">Hario V-60</string>
    <string name="title_activity_french_press">French Press</string>
    <string name="title_activity_iced_coffee">Iced Coffee</string>

    <!--hint resources-->
    <string name="hint_instructions_step_number">Step. 1</string>
    <string name="hint_instruction_step1_aeropress">Load filter over cover and screw onto bottom-half of brewer, set on top of a cup or carafe.</string>

    <!--Brew Methods Requirements-->
    <string name="serving">serving</string>
    <string name="brew_time">Brew Time</string>
    <string name="grind_setting">Grind Setting</string>
    <string name="brew_method_description">Description</string>
    <string name="brew_method_instructions">Instructions</string>

    <!--Grind sizes-->
    <string name="grind_size_fine">Fine</string>
    <string name="grind_size_medium">Medium</string>
    <string name="grind_size_coarse">Coarse</string>
    <integer name="default_serving_size">1</integer>
    <string name="small_device">Serving size has been changed to 1 on this brew method due to the nature of the method</string>

    <!--Resources for aeropress-->
    <string name="title_aeropress">Aeropress</string>]
    <string name="bio_aeropress">
        The aero-press, designed by the inventor of the Aerobie Ring (a flying ring), is a great light-weight travel companion loved by many in the coffee world. It can be used with a paper or metal filter and combines emersion and pressure brewing resulting in a full-bodied and fragrent cup.
    </string>
    <array name="instructions_aeropress_array">
        <item name="instruction_step1_aeropress">Load filter over cover and screw onto bottom-half
            of brewer, set on top of a cup or carafe.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step2_aeropress">Wet filter and warm brewer by pouring hot water
            into lower half.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step3_aeropress">Grind coffee on slightly finer grind than paper
            filter, dump hot water from carafe, positioning back under the brewer, and dump grounds
            into tube.>
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step4_aeropress">Pour INT UNITS of water into brewer, filling to the
            top.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step5_aeropress">Using a spoon, stir grounds at bottom of brewer
            gently.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step6_aeropress">Slide top half of brewer in bottom half, initially
            in an angle, and then straighten out into a vertical position.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step7_aeropress">At 1:00 remove entire setup off of scale, and
            gently press using just body weight. Complete press should finish at 1:30.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step8_aeropress">Stir coffee in carafe and serve.</item>
    </array>

    <!--Resources for frenchpress-->
    <string name="title_frenchpress">Frenchpress</string>]
    <string name="bio_frenchpress">
        The french press is perhaps the easiest brew-method to achieve a good tasting cup of coffee. The method a full-emersion technique and filters through a metal screen. The method has the biggest body/mouth feel due to the high amount of sediment that passes through the screen; this also results in muted acidity and nuanced flavors.
    </string>
    <array name="instructions_frenchpress_array">
        <item name="instruction_step1_frenchpress">Pour a small amount of hot water into the vessel
            to preheat.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step2_frenchpress">Grind the coffee on a course/french press
            setting.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step3_frenchpress">Pour out pre-heat water and dump in grounds.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step4_frenchpress">Start timer and pour in INT grams of water.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step5_frenchpress">With a spoon, stir wet grounds to fully expose to
            water.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step6_frenchpress">Let sit for 30 seconds.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step7_frenchpress">Last pour to finish at INT UNITS.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step8_frenchpress">At 4:00 minutes, gently press plunger to
            completion.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step9_frenchpress">Pour out all of coffee into cup or carraff to
            serve, leaving none left in the french press. Coffee left in the french press will
            continue to brew and could over extract.
        </item>
    </array>

    <!--Resources for hario V-60-->
    <string name="title_harioV60">Hario V-60</string>]
    <string name="bio_harioV60">
        The hario V-60 is capable of so much, but it is easy to mess up. When done right, the body is smooth and those bright acidic notes really shine through the cup. The V-60 is a pour-over drip with ridges on the walls of the vessel which allow for greater flow. Detail to your method of pouring is required and a gooseneck kettle is recommended.
    </string>
    <array name="instructions_harioV60_array">
        <item name="instruction_step1_harioV60">Place vessel either on top of coffee cup or on stand
            with cup/carafe below.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step2_harioV60">Crease the paper filter along the ridged edge, place
            the filter in the brewer and completely wet with hot water.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step3_harioV60">Grind the coffee on a V-60/paper filter setting,
            dump grounds in brewer, dump out hot water from cup/carafe.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step4_harioV60">Start timer and make initial pour of INT UNITS, take
            a spoon and stir the grounds to ensure that all grinds are wet. Let bloom.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step5_harioV60">At 45 seconds, slowly pour bringing the total amount
            of water to INT UNITS. When pouring, make small concentric circles in the center,
            ensuring to not touch the sides of the brewer. Pour should be 15 seconds finishing at
            1:00.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step6_harioV60">At 1:30 begin third pour, bringing the total amount
            of water to INT UNITS, finishing at 1:45.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step7_harioV60">At 2:00 begin the last pour, bringing the toal
            amount of water to INT UNITS, finishing at 2:15.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step8_harioV60">Coffee should finish dripping around 2:30-3:15,
            remove brewer and stir contents of cup to fully integrate the coffee.
        </item>
    </array>

    <!--Resources for chemex-->
    <string name="title_chemex">Chemex</string>]
    <string name="bio_chemex">Chemex is a design icon of the coffee world originally invented in 1941. The proprietary thick filter removes more oil and sediments from the coffee than any other brew method, leaving a smooth and acidic cup. Recommend using a gooseneck kettle for pouring water.</string>
    <array name="instructions_chemex_array">
        <item name="instruction_step1_harioV60">Place vessel either on top of coffee cup or on stand
            with cup/carafe below.
        </item>

        <item name="instruction_step2_chemex">Crease the paper filter along the ridged edge, place
            the filter in the brewer and completely wet with hot water.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step3_chemex">Grind the coffee on a V-60/paper filter setting, dump
            grounds in brewer, dump out hot water from cup/carafe.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step4_chemex">Start timer and make initial pour of INT UNITS, take a
            spoon and stir the grounds to ensure that all grinds are wet. Let bloom.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step5_chemex">At 45 seconds, slowly pour bringing the total amount
            of water to INT UNITS. When pouring, make small concentric circles in the center,
            ensuring to not touch the sides of the brewer. Pour should be 15 seconds finishing at
            1:00.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step6_chemex">At 1:30 begin third pour, bringing the total amount of
            water to INT UNITS, finishing at 1:45.

        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step7_chemex">At 2:00 begin the last pour, bringing the toal amount
            of water to INT UNITS, finishing at 2:15.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step8_chemex">Coffee should finish dripping around 2:30-3:15, remove
            brewer and stir contents of cup to fully integrate the coffee.
        </item>

    </array>

    <!--Resources for Iced Coffee-->
    <string name="title_cold_brew">Cold Brew</string>]
    <string name="bio_cold_brew">Cold brew coffee makes for a strong, full-bodied, iced coffee beverage. There are many different vessles to make cold brew in, this method can be used interchangeably on any of them.
</string>
    <array name="instructions_cold_brew_array">
        <item name="instruction_step1_cold_brew">Grind coffee on french press setting.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step2_cold_brew">Dump grounds into brewer.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step3_cold_brew">Add INT UNITS cold tap water.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step4_cold_brew">Stir ensuring to get all grounds wet.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step5_cold_brew">At 16-18 hours, stir grounds one more time and
            filter out coffee into a large carafe.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step6_cold_brew">Diltute with water. Recipe is generally 1:1
            coffee:water, but it is recommended to add the water to best taste.
            Store in refrigerater. Good for 7-10 Days. Serve with Ice.
        </item>
    </array>

    <!--Resources for Kalita Wave-->
    <string name="title_kalita_wave">Kalita Wave</string>]
    <string name="bio_kalita_wave">The Kalita Wave is can produce an awesome balanced and sweet cup of coffee. Its flat bottom causes an even extraction pulls out sweetness and body in the cup. This guide reccomends a coarse grind, and uses agitation to slow the brew time down.</string>
    <array name="instructions_kalita_wave">
        <item name="instruction_step1_kalita_wave">Bring water to a boil.</item>
        <item name="instruction_step2_kalita_wave">Rinse paper filter, retaining natural filter shape.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step3_kalita_wave">Grind the coffee on coarse setting, dump grounds in brewer, dump out hot water from cup/carafe.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step4_kalita_wave">Start timer and make initial pour of INT UNITS, take a spoon and stir the grounds to ensure that all grinds are wet. Let bloom.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step5_kalita_wave">At 45 seconds, quickly pour in a circular pattern bringing the total amount of water to INT UNITS.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step6_kalita_wave">Continue adding pulses of INT UNITS of water at a time, making sure to keep water bed elevated.
        </item>
        <item name="instruction_step7_kalita_wave">Coffee should finish dripping around 3:45 with INT UNITS as its final weight. remove brewer and stir contents of cup to fully integrate the coffee.</item>
    </array>

    <!--Resources for clock-->
    <string name="start_time">00:00</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset</string>

    <!-- Preference Resources -->
    <string name="imperial_system">Imperial (fluid ounces [not recommended])</string>
    <string name="metric_System">Metric (grams)</string>
    <string name="pref_serving_size_sum">The number of cups of coffee you\'d like to make: %s</string>

    <!-- Navigation Drawer List -->
    <string name="navigation_drawer_home">Home</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_recipe">Recipe</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="accessibility_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="accessibility_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">drawer open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">drawer close</string>
    <string name="title_activity_menu">MenuActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>

    <!--recipe fragment-->
    <string name="title_recipe">About the recipe</string>
    <string name="description_recipe">The recipes for all of these brew methods is based on a recipes that aim for a total dissolved solid (TDS) ratio of 1.38\-1.45. These recipes are great for a starting place but due to the variety in coffees and roasts, adjustments may be necessary.</string>
    <string name="accessability_image_description_recipe">Recipe chart showing extraction profile</string>

    <!--feedback fragment-->
    <string name="accessability_image_description_feedback">Feedback illustration</string>
    <string name="title_feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="title_donations">Donations</string>
    <string name="description_feedback">Got an idea to improve this app? Come across a bug I didn\'t find? Want to just talk about coffee or programming? Feel free to drop a line!</string>
    <string name="link_feedback">Send</string>
    <string name="description_donate">This app was written in my free time between being a student and working. There\'s no plan for a \"premium\" version of the app, but if you want, you can buy me coffee through the PayPal link below.</string>
    <string name="link_paypal">Donate with PayPal</string>
    <string name="edit_text_hint_name">Name</string>
    <string name="edit_text_hint_subject">Subject (Optional)</string>
    <string name="edit_text_hint_body">Body</string>
</resources>
